

CONTACT

- **** 09032300258
- → Pouyatirdad70@gmail.com
- Tehran, Sadeghiyeh
- <u>Linkedin</u>
- Github

SKILLS

- C#
- Entity Framework
- SQL Server
- .Net Framework & Core
- Design Patterns & Solid
- Unit Testing
- Domain Driven Design
- RabbitMQ
- Redis
- Docker
- HTML & CSS & Bootstrap
- SASS
- Git
- JQuery & JavaScript
- React

EDUCATION

since 2019

ISLAMIC AZAD UNIVERSITY

 Bachelor of IT Software Engineering

LANGUAGES

- Persian
- English
- German

POUYA TIRDAD

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Energetic and team-oriented developer with 4 years of experience in full development of .NET based systems. Interested in continuous learning and applying new technologies in the work environment, focusing on improving the quality and efficiency of products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DanaPardaz

2023 - 2024

Full Stack Developer

- My responsibilities included not only writing clean and efficient code, but also reviewing and updating applications to improve functionality and performance.
- I have extensive experience working with SQL Server as a primary database system, where I use stored procedures (SP), scheduled tasks and triggers to optimize data operations and ensure seamless data flow across applications.

Webone 2021 - 2022

Full Stack Developer

- I have played a key role in the digital development of companies by skillfully and meticulously designing and implementing more than 30 diverse websites.
- As a .NET developer, my engagement with SQL Server has been focused on grasping the foundational concepts of stored procedures (SP), triggers, and jobs. While my utilization of these elements has been limited, it has been instrumental in my understanding of database automation and event-driven data management. This knowledge has empowered me to optimize queries and enhance system efficiency progressively.

Spad 2020 - 2021

Frontend Developer

- I have worked as a Front End using HTML, CSS and JavaScript for 6 months, and I have been working in the Back End for 8 months with the C# language and the ASP.Net MVC framework that I learned there.
- In this company, the projects we were working on, a company, a store, we were working on a dedicated management panel (ASP. NET CORE) that was implemented by our own team (front and back).